{
    "id": "acc3ed2e92144af2b01d134e5ac8aa8d",
    "title": "Prepositions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He is partial ………………….. his relatives.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "with",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "08b1cb4063d44e7d82a32736b9317cb0"
        },
        {
            "question": "His infatuation ………………. her led him astray.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "for",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f91969a0f3d34d238e37b93339eecd1a"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have great respect ………………….. him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "with",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "2167880e0b4d40c3a9dbec7818e522ca"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is not qualified ………………….. the post.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "for",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "77ef81df24b34d80886ac30638758e1d"
        },
        {
            "question": "Illiteracy is a hindrance …………………. progress.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "to",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4519d15fa57540828496325b38322311"
        },
        {
            "question": "There are several benefits …………………. traveling alone.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "to",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7c29df924d2541f789e79d3025d9374c"
        },
        {
            "question": "He neither said nor did anything derogatory ………….………….. his position.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "to",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1b7e5b0d82cf4c6fb0070d85344b66d7"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is desirous …………………. going abroad.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "of",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "2578fbe7c3184fb68f320ee19c34a6f8"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is respectful ………………… his senior officers.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "to",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c96846138296410d900c1c0bb65629c2"
        },
        {
            "question": "He has no prejudice ………………….. foreigners.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "against",
                "before"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "efe21ef0ac68402e833fd4a8315857a5"
        }
    ]
}